[music]
All right, been a good two days.
Obviously, uh the red zone day here, you
know, clean up some stuff. Uh but I like
where the guys are at. You know, we got
to focus another day here and uh and get
ready to go. So excited about this
challenge.
>> Uh start with the safety situation.
Obviously Kirby and um Harper were, you
know, questionable going into the week.
You know, how have they progressed
through the week? to either to have a
chance of of playing on uh Sunday.
>> Well, I you know, Kirby had a setback,
so uh obviously not as um don't feel as
good about that. Harper uh will be out
there at practice today, so feel pretty
good about him, but we'll see. Uh there
again, I can't give you definitives
right now, but but that's kind of where
we're at. So, we'll be good. Look,
Howlet's been taking reps. Uh DT's been
taking reps. M's been taking rep. I
mean, we got, you know, we got plenty of
guys. Uh, and uh, they're getting
valuable reps, so we're good.
>> Is Kirby an IR candidate at this point?
He doesn't play in a couple months.
>> Could be. I mean, could be. We're We're
at the back end of the season now. So,
you know, anything, even if it's not
technically long-term, becomes longterm
because we don't have many games left.
So,
>> in terms of like was it that serious of
a setback? How would you define that?
>> Uh, no. I mean, it's just it, you know,
just Yeah, it's uh, you know,
bothers him, you know, that's the best
way to say it.
>> Uh, this be the the third year in a row
you guys have played [clears throat] LA
in what feels like a really big game. Do
you feel like you've developed, you
know, trade aside, like a familiarity, a
rivalry with this team just from playing
them in so many big games? Uh I mean I I
don't I think there there is um I think
I I think we are somewhat familiar as
they are with us because we have played
in the last three years or going on
three years here. Um so I think there is
something to that. Now that being said
they've evolved. You know they're doing
things a little bit different in areas.
Um, [snorts] you know, the things
they're doing defensively, they're
they're more crisp than they were last
year cuz, you know, uh, Shoula's taking
over over there. He's doing a great job.
And, man, they're a year another year
into what how he wants to do it and how
they they wanted to get done. So,
they're they're more advanced or more
involved. A lot of those guys were pups
or younger players, man. They've grown
another year. So, right, they're they
they've elevated uh what they do. And
then offensively, like we talked about,
a lot more 13 personnel than what it was
last year when we played them or even
the year before that. So, there's things
and we're we're different, too. I mean,
we're we're different in some areas,
too. So, uh but as far as personnel, the
guys, you know, uh you have a pretty
good idea. We got a pretty good idea
what it's like toe-to-toe with Stafford,
you know, with with Nua, you know, with
um with a number of those guys over
there. You know, we played Turner, you
know, we we played Verse and those guys.
They're again a year older. So, I think
there is something to that, but it's
always a chess game and you're always
trying to find the matchups. Uh, they're
doing it, we're doing it, and and you do
it, and then you let the guys go play.
>> Specifically with Stafford, is he uh how
high level of football are you seeing
from him on tape right now.
>> I mean, he's playing as good as anybody
at the position right now. That's that's
the bottom line. I mean, he's um you
know, and a number of things they're
doing with him, I think, are are great.
You know, they really are. There's a ton
of under center turning his back to the
defense, man. play action pass. Uh, you
know, he he's like our guy, he's got
pinpoint accuracy. He sees it, man. He
can rip it. Um, you know, obviously he
he's seen everything you can see
defensively. He knows the looks. Um, but
he's he is he's playing at a high level.
If we if we don't disrupt him, uh, it
it'll be it'll be a long day. It'll be a
long day. So, we we have to we got to
shut down the run as usual, and we got
to find a way to disrupt this guy if we
can because he's dangerous. throws a ton
of he throws a ton of 50/50 balls to
both those guys. Um I think it takes
maybe a different mindset from a
quarterback to trust his receivers in
that regard. When when you're playing
cornerback against that, how [snorts]
how different is the the coverage
element of it when when you even when
maybe you have them covered through 90%
[snorts] of the route, they're still not
necessarily covered?
>> Yeah. Well, I think like any any of
these that come up, um, and our DBs know
this, you know, and I tell them, Shep
tells them, Shay tells them, listen, you
may get beat on one, but make it hard.
You know, if they make some catch that's
going to go all over social media. Well,
good for them. You know, that's a hell
of a play, but make sure they're having
to make that with you all over them or
you turn to the ball, you in their hip
pocket, and they come away. If you do
that, man, I'll take our guy, you know,
I'll take our guy eight out of 10 of
those. Like, we'll make that play as
long as we make it hard. Now, that
doesn't mean they won't come up with
one. And he does. He gives his guys a
chance to make a play, but that's okay.
You know, uh, you make it hard on them.
Make them earn that if that's if that's
the way it's going to be. Big big
picture wise, I mean, how concerned are
you long term about the safety situation
given, you know, Kirby and Brian are
arguably the best safety combo in the
league? And then, you know, they were
obviously a big part of the future plans
and just even how you structured the
defense.
>> Honestly, I'm not I'm really not I mean,
I hate losing either one of those
players. They're great players. They're
great teammates. They're great. But as
far as wor I'm really not worried. I I
really do trust the guys that are going
back there for us. I I do, man. And what
you lose in a couple areas, you may gain
in other areas having some of these guys
back there, you know. So, um, so I know
I'm good.
>> As it relates to even next year, you
know, the years after.
>> Listen, I I can't even get the next year
right now. I Yeah, I'm not even thinking
about next year right now. My focus is
right now LA and then beyond. You know,
once we get through this one, then then
we're on to the next one.
>> Were you aware were you aware of
Stafford when he was coming up through
like Texas High School? Like as a fellow
Texan yourself? What kind of floor did
he occupy in in the state of Texas?
>> Yeah, I of course I was aware of him
from afar. I mean, you you um you know,
as you guys know, I mean, football in
Texas is I mean, it's a big thing. It's
a big deal. And uh he was playing at a
high level. It was actually one of
those, you know, um like man, he
freaking left the state, you know,
that's what you think like, uh I'm an
Aggie or, you know, uh you stay at, you
know,&M or Texas or, you know, um so
that that hurt more than anything is the
fact that he left and went to Georgia,
you know, but uh you you're very well
aware of the type of player he is and uh
yeah, he's he's one of those guys, man.
He put up some uh some crazy numbers and
had a lot of success in high school.
13 personnel been a big topic this week.
I I know you guys like to use base a
lot, so maybe you're well equipped to to
match up with that. But when you're kind
of tasked with slowing down [snorts] an
innovative thing, like where do you do
you look to the past to try and find a
way to stop or I guess how do you just
see what other teams are doing this
season? How do you begin to attack?
Well, yeah. I think a ton of the cutups
are, you know, you're you're getting to
see what some teams have had some
success with. And and I'll be honest
with you, they've they've uh not many
people have been able to stop them or or
slow them down. So, I I will be the
first to admit that. But yet, there are
some nuggets you can find in there with
what some of these teams have done um
that have at least made it hard for
them. Um and you take some of that and
and I do feel like personnel-wise we're
set up pretty good to handle to handle
some of this. And and look, I'll bring
it up again. The great equalizer is,
man, you hammer the run and you you get
the ball out. You do that and uh and it
changes a lot of things. So, we we and
that's man, that's effort and that's a
conscious effort to go after the ball.
So, uh we got to do that again.
>> With uh with Tom Kennedy, how early in
your coaching tenure did you identify
him as someone who kind of fit the mold
and identity of what you guys wanted to
be? I mean, that was whatever the first
training camp. I mean, you know, you
could uh I think you just knew the kid's
a football player. He's not a kid. He's
a man. I mean, he he's he's a football
player. He's instinctive. He could play
all the positions. Every time he had a
chance to make a play or get in position
to make a play, made a play. Um and uh
and he's he's just he's always done
that. You know, he's always done it. And
you know, you you know, there's all
these circumstances that come into play
and uh the guy's overcome a ton and and
he knows and I've said it. I'm like, you
you know,
there's an argument, you've earned your
right. Every year on the roster, you've
earned that right. But so much of it is,
like we've said, you're trying to put
together the best 69man roster that you
can. And and that's where sometimes that
that falls into it. And to his credit,
he just continues to go back to work. He
gets on the vet squad. He kicks ass in
practice, gives a great look. We throw
him in on our offense. You know, if one
of our guys needs a blow, he goes in at
the F. He goes in at the Z. He goes in
at the X with golf and just he he
crushes it, right? So when his numbers
called, we don't miss a beat. Like we
trust him. That's why Green Bay when we
lost Saint, we just we put TK right in
that spot. We didn't move around. Okay,
we need to put Tesla here and put JMO
here. We just put TK right there. like
he he becomes saint. Um so it's there's
a tremendous amount of trust that he's
got with myself, the coaches, and with
golf, which is uh significant
>> with with it being red zone day. Just
what makes them so good defensively in
the red zone? I think teams are only at
43% against them, second best in the
league. Just what is it about what they
do in the red zone that's so tough?
>> First of all, there's not very many
reps. They there's not a lot of red zone
reps, period. you start going through
that cut up and you're like, man, not
many teams are getting down there and
when they do the it's hard. Um, it's
hard. I would tell you this, they're
they they they're not going to let you
run the ball. Like that's the mentality.
Just the the way that they they're
they're going to try to get bigger than
you at times. Once you get, you know, to
a certain point down there tight enough,
they'll get bigger than you and and or
they're going to shut down the gaps by
the way they pressure. you know, they're
going to make you uh they're going to
make you have to do something you don't
want to do. And really, most teams, if
you can run the ball, that's where you
have success in the red zone is is
running the football. So, they take away
what you do best and force you to throw
it in tight spaces, tight areas. Um, you
know, so they're they're good, man. And
their personnel is set up to they're
strong in the middle. They're
disruptive. And then they can they can
set edges with those those edge
defenders, and that makes it that makes
it tough.
Okay.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]